This is Surokkha AI — an AI safety app for women in Bangladesh.
Paste any suspicious message — it tells you if it's a scam, and why.
First example — a bKash fraud message, written in Banglish.
A red alert — 99% risk. It explains: asks for OTP, threatens to block the account.
Now a romance / marriage scam — fully in Bangla.
Another alert. It catches the fast marriage proposal, the "abroad" promise, and the money request — exactly how real scams work.
But it doesn't cry wolf. Let's try an ordinary message.
Green — safe. No false alarm. That trust is what keeps people using it.
Your own text works too — here, a grooming attempt in Banglish.
Caught it — pressure to keep secrets and move to a private app.
It works in 3 layers — fast rules, an AI model that reads Bangla, Banglish and English, and a layer that explains the reason.
Your messages are never stored. Next, the model runs fully on-device — completely private.
Truecaller catches spam calls — Surokkha AI catches dangerous conversations. Thank you.